Hi, my name is Lauren and today, I'm going to discuss hair drying tips.
After you get out of the shower, you're, and you wring out most of the moisture from your hair, you're going to take your damp hair, you're going to place a little product in it.
Emulsify the product really well within your hands, go through the ends of your hair first, and then work your way towards the root in order to prevent putting too much product, and give, giving your hair more of a greasier look.
If you're in trying to keep volume, what you're going to do is put a root lifter, if you have one, and then you can just spray that.
That's the only product that will goes essentially, only by the root.
Once you've done and placed your product in, you are actually going to lift your hair and direct your hair to where you want it to go.
Your hair, because of your own natural body heat, will dry by the root quicker.
So, rather than section it when it's very wet and getting, starting from the bottom and working your way up, you're not going to achieve the volume that you may want on the top.
You're going to lift your hair in smaller sections, using your hands.
Focus your blow dryer onto your root and work your way onto your root and work your way up from your root to your mid-shafts.
You are going to do this all throughout your entire head, in order to promote volume and get the shape that you want on your hair.
Once your hair is about eighty percent dry, that's when it'll really start taking shape.
I recommend maybe use a clip.
Clip the hair, section some of the others out of the way.
Get a round brush, if that you want to tri...curl it under.
It can either be, it should be ceramic based in order to kind of heat up the ceramic.
You're going to roll it in, almost as if it was a curler.
You're going to heat up the ceramic with the hot air and then you're going to use the cool button.
The cool button is going to set in the style that you are looking to have.
So if you were looking to roll it under, it will actually help your hair stay there.
So you're just going to pull your hair out.
Release the brush when it's done and it should bevel under.
You will do this for the rest of your hair.
As long as you dry about eighty percent beforehand, you will be fine and it will cut down on your drying time and it'll make it a lot quicker and a lot more effective.
And that is tips on drying your hair.